{
    "subject": "resource/Elena_Gerhardt",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Elena Gerhardt (11 November 1883 \u2013 11 January 1961) was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, of which she was considered one of the great interpreters. She left Germany for good to live in London in October 1934.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Elena Gerhardt is that she was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, and she left Germany for good to live in London in October 1934.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8314939141273499,
            "question": "What prompted Elena Gerhardt to leave Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7987066507339478,
            "question": "Where did Elena Gerhardt move to in October 1934?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7834958434104919,
            "question": "What type of singer was Elena Gerhardt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644748091697693,
            "question": "When did Elena Gerhardt leave Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7632655501365662,
            "question": "Was Elena Gerhardt a famous singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7570000886917114,
            "question": "Elena Gerhardt's singing style is often associated with which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722852885723114,
            "question": "What year did Elena Gerhardt leave Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228057742118835,
            "question": "Where was Elena Gerhardt based before she moved to London?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6143519878387451,
            "question": "What kind of music was Elena Gerhardt known for performing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5788316130638123,
            "question": "What nationality was Elena Gerhardt?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Elena Gerhardt is that she was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, and she left Germany for good to live in London in October 1934.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1646_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music was Elena Gerhardt known for performing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1646_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Elena Gerhardt based before she moved to London?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1646_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Elena Gerhardt leave Germany?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1646_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1646_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple states that Elena Gerhardt was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, and she left Germany for good to live in London in October 1934.\n\nThis statement is supported by multiple documents, including:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1646/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1646/re-ranker-msmarco/91.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1646/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1646/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt\n\nAll of these documents mention that Elena Gerhardt was a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, and that she left Germany for good to live in London in October 1934."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the comment about Elena Gerhardt being a German mezzo-soprano singer associated with the singing of German classical lieder, and leaving Germany for good to live in London in October 1934."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}